const mikeQuestions = 
{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Prior to its redevelopment, Manchester’s St Peter’s Square was home to a small garden; what was its name?",
      "correct_answer": "Manchester Peace Garden",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Manchester Central Garden",
        "The Elizabeth Gaskell Gardens",
        "The War Memorial Garden"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which band did the following people all play in: Jimmy Page, Jeff Beck, Eric Clapton?",
      "correct_answer": "The Yardbirds",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Small Faces",
        "Cream",
        "The Bluesbreakers"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is Andy’s favourite alcohol percentage for a beer?",
      "correct_answer": "4%",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "7%",
        "5.5%",
        "2.8%"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What was the first date of the lockdown?",
      "correct_answer": "23rd March",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1st April",
        "17th March",
        "28th March"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Why is the sky blue?",
      "correct_answer": "Because the gases in the air scatter sunlight and blue light is scattered more than other types of light due to its shorter wave length",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Because the air contains mostly nitrogen which is blue in large enough volumes",
        "Because of the reflective properties of certain particles in the air which reflect the ocean",
        "Because the radiation from the Sun’s rays cause the electrons in the gases in the Earth’s atmosphere to vibrate, giving off a blue shimmer"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Brass is an alloy of which metals?",
      "correct_answer": "Copper and zinc",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Copper and iron",
        "Copper and lead",
        "Copper and aluminium"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is Madonna’s real first name?",
      "correct_answer": "Madonna",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ruth",
        "Juliet",
        "Sonya"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who won the first World Cup?",
      "correct_answer": "Uruguay",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Argentina",
        "Paraguay",
        "Brazil"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What’s my favourite type of fruit?",
      "correct_answer": "Pineapple",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Orange",
        "Apple",
        "Passion Fruit"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the best form of defence?",
      "correct_answer": "Attack",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Defence",
        "Never going out",
        "The pork sword"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In which year did the TV show Rick & Morty first grace our screens with its unwelcome presence?",
      "correct_answer": "2013",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2015",
        "2012",
        "2014"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In the song El Condor Pasa made famous by Simon and Garfunkel, what does Paul Simon sing he would rather be then a snail?",
      "correct_answer": "A sparrow",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "He doesn't sing it, Art Garfunkel does",
        "A spider",
        "A snake"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What's the best way to impress someone on Tinder?",
      "correct_answer": "Bake a big cake decorated with characters from your favourite film with icing and set it as your third profile picture",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Google 'best Tinder opening lines' and use one of those",
        "Have photos taken of yourself with an assortment of sedated wild animals (the more dangerous the better)",
        "Wait 2 days after you match then send a template message, and if they send a good reply then wait 1 day and send a short reply back followed by a long reply, but if they send a short reply to your first message then apologise for your first message as it wasn't up to standard and if they don't reply to that apologise for apologising"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In what year did Greggs stop selling meat & potato pasties?",
      "correct_answer": "2019",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2020",
        "2018",
        "2017"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the main flavour of the tasty French drink, pastis?",
      "correct_answer": "Aniseed",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Baguette",
        "Raspberry",
        "Grape"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the main type of monkey I worked with in South America?",
      "correct_answer": "Capuchin",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Macaque",
        "Tamarin",
        "Spider monkey"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the best form of flattery?",
      "correct_answer": "'Mistakenly' sending someone you like a text meant for a friend in which you say nice things about them and then message back apologising and saying you're really embarrassed, that text was obviously meant for someone else haha",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Telling someone you love them on the first date",
        "Telling someone they have nice eyes or hair or mouth or whatever",
        "Messaging someone constantly even when they don't reply"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which of the following trees is a hardwood?",
      "correct_answer": "Oak",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Pine",
        "Spruce",
        "Yew"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is the best of the following Simpsons characters?",
      "correct_answer": "Hans Moleman",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Troy McClure",
        "Rod Flanders",
        "Reverend Lovejoy"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which of these is not the title of a well-known book?",
      "correct_answer": "Alice in Wonderland",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Gravity's Rainbow",
        "The Last of the Mohicans",
        "Mrs Dalloway"
      ]
    }
  ]
}


export default mikeQuestions